<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>don't know what it is on Pippimotta</title><link>http://pippimotta.github.io/categories/dont-know-what-it-is/</link><description>Recent content in don't know what it is on Pippimotta</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://pippimotta.github.io/categories/dont-know-what-it-is/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cheat Sheet for self introduction</title><link>http://pippimotta.github.io/post/self_intro_cheatsheet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://pippimotta.github.io/post/self_intro_cheatsheet/</guid><description>This is just the longer version of about &amp;ndash; I am not good at self-introduction, and feel absolutely confused at 80% of the circumstance if I am required to do one. However, I happen to have a slightly complicated story to tell. So I decide to write this cheat sheet to see whether this can make things easier. I am trying to make it FAQ-like cuz I kind of being keen on guessing people&amp;rsquo;s questions (bad habit) (^^)</description></item><item><title>The Legend of Zelda: Breath of the Wild as a site of knowledge</title><link>http://pippimotta.github.io/post/zelda/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://pippimotta.github.io/post/zelda/</guid><description>&lt;p>It seems hard to add any more compliments to &lt;em>The Legend of Zelda: Breath of the Wild&lt;/em>. This action-adventure game issued in March 2017, developed and published by Nintendo won the IGN’s Game of the Year.
It is described as “evocative, exhilarating and a masterclass in open-world design” and the milestone in the game history. The game, just as its tile indicated, creates a wild and vast area –the land of &lt;em>Hyrule&lt;/em> for the players, which hides hundreds of puzzles and wonder to be found.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>