<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>migration on Pippimotta</title><link>http://pippimotta.github.io/categories/migration/</link><description>Recent content in migration on Pippimotta</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://pippimotta.github.io/categories/migration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>令和三年三月十三日、海を見に行く</title><link>http://pippimotta.github.io/post/seeing_the_ocean/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://pippimotta.github.io/post/seeing_the_ocean/</guid><description>&lt;p>Last Saturday, I went on my first road trip with Capybara. We passed through the belly of the mountains all the way to the southern tip of the cape.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I think this is the first time I saw such a wild sea, gulping clouds and sea breeze, manipulating sun and rain, wild and proud, without any trace of human domestication, no sand or pebbles to be found, only dark reefs barely marking the boundary between sea and land, like a monk in silent meditation, bearing the low roar of the waves leaping, crashing, and then breaking on top of the skull, which is intimidating anyone who tries to intimate with it with white fragments. The back of the whale seems to appear at the junction of the sky and the sea in the next moment. The smell of the sea is pure and clean, and the tiny particles that roll into the nose spread the will of an ancient body of water: the sea does not need a declaration, does not need an oracle, and cannot be interpreted. Or maybe the sea itself is an oracle.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Legend of Zelda: Breath of the Wild as a site of knowledge</title><link>http://pippimotta.github.io/post/zelda/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://pippimotta.github.io/post/zelda/</guid><description>&lt;p>It seems hard to add any more compliments to &lt;em>The Legend of Zelda: Breath of the Wild&lt;/em>. This action-adventure game issued in March 2017, developed and published by Nintendo won the IGN’s Game of the Year.
It is described as “evocative, exhilarating and a masterclass in open-world design” and the milestone in the game history. The game, just as its tile indicated, creates a wild and vast area –the land of &lt;em>Hyrule&lt;/em> for the players, which hides hundreds of puzzles and wonder to be found.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Hiking</title><link>http://pippimotta.github.io/post/mountain_climbing/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://pippimotta.github.io/post/mountain_climbing/</guid><description>&lt;p>Today I went to climb the mountain again! Heiligenberg is a great moutain, with few people and lots of plants and insects. I saw hops, young and premature acorns, hidden mosses and fern empires, and inky blue gastropod beetles, who especially love to sunbathe and are happy to hobble across the mountain and put their lives under the soles of pedestrians&amp;rsquo; shoes and bicycle wheels. One part of the road was densely covered with shiny metallic fragments of sheath wings, which was sad to see. I also ran into a Magcargo who was out walking at dusk on a clear day, as well as other goose-yellow mushrooms.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>